

NGUYEN QUANG THANG

DATA ANALYST



Majoring in International Economics, I am looking forward to improving my knowledge as well as experiences in data related area and willing to seize opportunities to develop career.

Becoming an official staff and a senior Data Analyst in 5 years

Contact information

13/10/2001

thangnguyen.t186@gmail.com

0354630663

Facebook: /thang.nguyenquang.7543/

Nam Tu Liem, Hanoi, Vietnam

Skills

• Language

Efficiency in English (all 4 skills)

• Computer

Efficiency in Microsoft Office
Basic knowledge in SQL and Power BI
Python (Pandas, Matplotlib, Numpy...) and other
statistics tools (STATA, Eviews)
Knowledge in econometrics models

References

Nguyen Ngoc Minh - minhnn04.fbn@gmail.com President of Future Bankers Network 2020-2021 Lookstore Human Resources

Certificate

• IELTS APTIS C in general

hr.lookstore@gmail.com

IELTS APTIS

Education

• Major: International Economics

Foreign Trade University August 2019- Present

Current GPA: 3.29/4

Work experience

Sales Staff

LOOK STORE | November 2020- March 2021

Main responsibilities:

- Consulting and doing customer service
- Being trained to communicate and handle unpredictable situation

Activities

Member of Future Bankers Network (FBN - FTU)

Specialization Department | October 2020- January 2022

- Organize monthly events, network with UB Academy and Faculty of Banking and Finance
- Research and give preliminary analysis of banking sector
- In charge of expertise at The Banker 2021